# **IHOR VOITIUK**

# **Python Developer**

## **CONTACTS**

+31 630 210 297

GitHub

# Hybrid, Remote, Office

ihorvoitiukk@gmail.com

<u>LinledIn</u>

Dedeemsvaart, NL

### **SUMMARY**

Motivated Python Developer with strong skills in both web development and data analysis. Specialized in web scraping, API development, and frontend/backend technologies. Passionate about programming, quick to learn, and an effective problem-solver. Demonstrated reliability and a proactive, goal-oriented approach, making me a valuable team player.

## **SKILLS**

Languages: Python, JavaScript

Frontend: HTML, CSS/SCSS, Vue.js

Backend Frameworks: Django, FastAPI / Node.js (familiar)
Web Scraping: Requests, AIOHTTP, Selenium, BeautifulSoup
Data Analysis and Scientific Computing: NumPy, Pandas

Database: MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Redis

Testing: unittest, pytest / Postman

Version control: Git, GitHub, Bitbucket

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### Junior Python Developer at BLUE-BI SYSTEM

10/2023 - Present | Hoogeveen, Netherlands

Hybrid | Full-time

**Developing software for productivity and efficiency** 

With expertise in both backend and frontend development, my duties involve designing, developing, and enhancing applications, debugging, and sometimes refactoring code to incorporate the latest technologies.

**Technologies:** Python, JavaScript, HTML, CSS/SCSS, Vue.js, AngularJS, Django, Django Rest Framework, FastApi, NumPy, MySQL, MongoDB, Bitbucket

#### Junior Python Developer at ADOREYES

07/2023 - Present | Canada

Remote | Part time

**Cosmetic industry** 

I specialize in collecting and analyzing data from web pages to extract relevant information.

Technologies: Python, AIOHTTP, Requests, Selenium, BeautifulSoup, Pandas, MongoDB, Excel, GitHub

## **EDUCATION**

Python Developer Master's degree in Finance, banking and insurance

Go IT Academy THE NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF WATER AND

2022-2023 | Kyiv, Ukraine ENVIRONMENTAL ENGINEERING

Focus: Python core | Python Web | Data Science 2016 - 2021 | Rivne, Ukraine

## **LANGUAGES**

Ukrainian: Native Russian: Advanced (C1)

English: Intermediate (B1)

Dutch: Beginner